Lens
We wanted to make a movie about Hitler,
his rise to power and then his
inevitable demise.
Studio loved it.
The cast was set and the script was
incredible,
but we couldn't find anybody
in Hollywood that would play Hitler.
Nobody wanted to do it.
We looked
everywhere, but no one wanted to risk
their careers,
but
we did find one person.
I'm Hitler.
They didn't have anyone to play Hitler.
So, they called me. The
studio called me. They said, "Donald,
could you please get us out of this?"
He sent me 27 voicemails.
Hello, Lauren. This is Donald Trump
and I can be Hitler here. Watch.
Bad Jews, not good.
Lauren, It's Donald again. If I need
to be naked in this,
which Hitler was,
he was naked quite a bit.
I I do have a
guy as a replacement. He has a big
piece.
He took a perfectly good script.
And he improved the whole thing.
Look at the size of this crowd. We've
got a lot of Jews here.
I don't think he ever read the script.
That guy right there, he's a Jew.
No, I'm kidding. Don't get him.
We could do
something about the Jews. I might not, but we could.
We've got big trains,
beautiful trains.
We could get them on
there, but I'm not going to kill the Jews.
I want to work with them. Is that
so bad?
I didn't like all the Jew stuff in the script.
If I was to put anyone on a
train, it would be crooked Hillary.
I wanted Hitler's failure as an artist
to be part of his evil origin story.
But then, you know, when I brought that up
to Trump, he said,
"Art is gay.
Art is gay."
Adolf Hitler was gay for doing art.
I don't do art. I make money.
We didn't realize how toxic it would be
for the rest of the cast.
It was the
worst set I've ever been on, ever.
We're
going to round up the Jews and what
we're going to do
is we're going to ask
them for some advice.
We're going to say, "Please help. We
need your help with our economy
right
now. Our economy is low. We need it big.
We need big economy.
We need more Jews."
Totally unprofessional.
It was a comp, a struggle to get through
anything.
No, no, no, no, no, no. We're doing a
holocaust.
We're going to kill Jews and
Poles.
Okay, cut.
Eight months I trained for
this role.
Method acting as a Nazi.
My wife traumatized in the bedroom.
Do you have any idea?
The things that I've looked up
on the internet, the things that I've said.
I can no longer go into Einstein
Brothers Bagels.
He he he got he got rid of Eva Braun
and Hitler's girlfriend. I don't know if
you've seen her. If you've seen
pictures,
not good. She was a bit of a dog.
Let me tell you something. I've got
a new Ava Braun and she's hot.
Bring her
out, Ava. Come on.
I had just got done eating a waitress's
[ __ ] at Buffalo Wild Wings and I said,
"Wow, you should be Ava Braun.
Look at her. Look at her. Am I right,
people?"
I met her at my restaurant, Hitler's. I
just opened it. You guys should stop by.
He started a fake restaurant in a movie
and then made a commercial for it.
Wow. Hitler's. What a fine restaurant.
We've got chicken wings and [ __ ] What
else is there?
Don't attack Jews. Instead, drink bruise.
That's what we say. Isn't that
funny?
This was my shining moment.
I need the Holocaust.
Oh, he said he liked the Holocaust.
Not that I would need it to have
happened.
You seem to be very eager for a
Holocaust. Crybaby Gerbles.
I'm not a crybaby. I'm not a crybaby.
Joe Crybaby Gerbles is a huge [ __ ]
All he wants to do is a Holocaust.
Could we get rid of this guy?
I've got a couple people's numbers. as we could
call The Rock.
I got fired.
He wanted the movie to be He
never kills himself.
He's good.
And eventually he helps the US defeat Japan.
I said, "Fine."
The United States called. They said, "We
like what you're doing here."
They said,
"Can you help us end this war with Japan?"
So I called Japan. I said,
"Hiroito."
I said, "You better slow down."
He told
me, "We'll never surrender."
That's how
he, you know, we'll never surrender.
I said, "I bet you do." That's what I think.
Sure enough, the next day, I
bombed the [ __ ] out of him.
He literally
harnessed the sun and threw it at them,
Japan.
He hit him with the sun. And let me tell
you, they didn't like it. They were running around.
Maybe now they'll get
their act together.
Maybe they'll stop
using swords and start building VCRs.
What?
2 a.m. I think Hitler should
eventually become president of US
cuz
Truman begs him. You know he would.
Truman was [ __ ]
Lol.
My work here in Germany is done.
I am taking the position of President Hitler
of the United States.
Thank you and good night Nazi Germany.
It was devastating. It was hard.
As an artist, you write a movie that you think
is going to is going to be impactful.
Stop stop looking at the camera.
And you know, he just took it and made a, you
know, made a movie that
made so much
money.
I was the best president.
I was the best Hitler.
We've got great
wings. Some of the best wings.
Medium, mild,
hot, genocide.
We've got [ __ ] everywhere.
I'm the best President Hitler.